My name's Conan Edogawa!
Meu nome é Conan Edogawa!
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a drug that shrunk him!
Shinichi, do ensino médio,
Although smaller, my mind remains that of a sharp detective!
Mesmo pequeno, minha inteligência continua genial!
Today's case is a two-part story aboard a luxury liner!
O caso de hoje é em duas partes e é sobre um navio de luxo!
Think you can tell who did it just from Part 1?
Consegue achar o culpado só vendo a primeira?
There's always only one truth!
A verdade é sempre única!
The first end of the century in 100 years
O primeiro fim de século em cem anos
When told to cry, I laughed instead
Quando me mandaram chorar, eu ri
The first end of the century in a long, long time
O primeiro fim do século em muito, muito tempo
We're leaping into a wide open world
Estamos saltando rumo a um mundo aberto
The things I tried to understand as a child
As coisas que eu tentava entender quando era criança
remain a mystery even as an adult
Continuam um mistério para mim como adulto
I'm neither a hotshot nor especially great
Não sou um figurão nem grande coisa
All I understand is the pounding of my heart
Eu só entendo as batidas do meu coração
It's neither an answer nor the truth
Não é uma resposta, tampouco a verdade
All I have faith in is the pounding of my heart
Eu só acredito nas batidas do meu coração
That and nothing else
E nada mais
What a beautiful view!
Que vista linda!
We sure were lucky! I was worried for a while there!
Que sorte a gente teve! Por um segundo fiquei preocupada!
Yeah!
É!
He forgot what time our return ship left,
Ele esqueceu que horas o nosso navio de volta saiu,
so we got to ride on this big one instead!
então pegamos esse grandão!
It was a good thing this ship just happened to stop at the island.
Que sorte que por acaso este navio estava atracado na ilha.
We would've been stranded out there for 3 days if it hadn't.
Senão, a gente ficaria ilhado por três dias.
But I wonder what kind of people would reserve a ship like this...
Mas que tipo de pessoa reserva um navio destes?
Is something the matter?
Algum problema?
No, it's nothing...
Não, não é nada...
I was just thinking about my parents who died in an accident last year...
Estava só pensando nos meus pais,
I wish they could've seen me all dressed up today...
Queria que eles me vissem vestida assim hoje...
All dressed up?
Vestida assim?
Is something wrong, Natsue?
Algum problema, Natsue?
Takeshi-san!
Takeshi!
The two of us were married today!
Nós dois nos casamos hoje!
Married?!
Casaram?
We had our ceremony this morning on Hatamoto Island,
A cerimônia foi hoje de manhã na ilha Hatamoto,
Shoichi's 2nd daughter Hatamoto Natsue (22) Natsue's Husband Hatamoto Takeshi (24)
2ª filha do Shoichi Natsue Hatamoto (22)
the same island you were on!
a mesma ilha onde vocês estavam!
Congratulations!
Parabéns!
But why did you have it on the island?
Mas por que na ilha?
The majority of the island belongs to the Hatamoto family.
A maior parte da ilha é propriedade da família Hatamoto.
We honor generations of our ancestors there.
Nós honramos gerações de nossos ancestrais lá.
It's a Hatamoto family tradition to hold wedding ceremonies on the island.
É tradição da família Hatamoto realizar os casamentos na ilha.
You fool!
Seu tolo!
We reserved this boat for ourselves, so what are strangers doing on it?!
Nós reservamos este navio para nós,
I'm sorry!
Desculpe!
They appeared to be stranded, so...
Parecia que eles tinham ficado ilhados, então...
How dare you go over my head!
Como se atreve a decidir sem meu consentimento?
You must think pretty highly of yourself
Você deve ser muito convencido
Mariko's husband Hatamoto Kitaro (47) Head of the Hatamoto family Hatamoto Go (72)
Marido da Mariko Kitaro Hatamoto (47)
if you're making decisions without approval.
para tomar decisões sem aprovação.
No, of course I don't!
É claro que não!
Don't worry about it.
Não se preocupe.
He's been in a bad mood since the ceremony today.
Ele está de mau humor desde a cerimônia.
Yes, after he ate my food...
Sim, depois que comeu a minha comida...
Uncle Joji!
Tio Joji!
I knew he hated Western-style food, but I had no idea he'd get that angry.
Eu sabia que ele não gostava de comida ocidental,
You call this food?!
Você chama isso de comida?
It seems my skills still aren't up to par.
Parece que minhas habilidades ainda não são boas.
Second son of the Hatamoto family Hatamoto Joji (41)
Segundo filho da família Hatamoto Joji Hatamoto (41)
Don't say that!
Não diga isso!
It was really delicious!
Estava uma delícia!
Say, lady-killer... What's with the flower?
Ei, mulherengo... Qual é a dessa flor?
Oh, Natsue put it there on the way back from the ceremony.
Ah, a Natsue pôs aqui voltando da cerimônia.
It's always been my dream since I was a little girl
Desde criança, meu sonho sempre foi
to give my beloved this flower that only grows on that island.
dar ao meu amado as flores que só crescem na ilha.
Too bad it wasn't me...
Filho único do Kitaro Ichiro Hatamoto (21)
Kitaro's only son Hatamoto Ichiro (21)
Que pena que não fui eu...
Like father, like son!
Tal pai, tal filho!
How long are you going to let him pretend to be an artist?!
Até quando vai deixar que ele finja que é artista?
You're his father, talk some sense into him!
Você é o pai, bote juízo na cabeça do seu filho!
Tell him to give up his hopeless dream!
Diga pra ele desistir desse sonho sem futuro!
Yes!
Sim!
Takeshi-kun!
Takeshi!
Yes?
Sim?
I need a word with you! Come to my room later!
Preciso dar uma palavrinha! Venha pro meu quarto depois!
Yes, sir...
Sim, senhor.
Just have patience, dear.
Tenha paciência, querido.
He isn't long for this world-- he'll be gone soon enough.
Ele não vai viver para sempre.
Eldest Hatamoto daughter, Kitaro's wife, Hatamoto Mariko (43)
E quando ele se for, toda a fortuna dos Hatamoto será sua!
And when he is, nearly all of the Hatamoto fortune will be yours!
Primogênita dos Hatamoto, esposa do Kitaro Mariko Hatamoto (43)
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
Eu não teria tanta certeza.
What's that supposed to mean?!
Por que diz isso?
Akie-san! Do you know something I don't?!
Akie, você sabe de algo que eu não sei?
Shoichi's daughter & Natsue's sister Hatamoto Akie (26)
Filha do Shoichi e irmã da Natsue Akie Hatamoto (26)
Don't be too shocked when you hear.
Não fique boquiaberta quando ouvir.
Impossible! That can't be true!
Impossível! Não pode ser!
It sounds like Grandfather's going to make the announcement
Parece que o vô vai anunciar
when we get back to Tokyo.
assim que voltarmos a Tóquio.
Gimme a break.
Dá um tempo.
Akie's husband Hatamoto Tatsuo (26)
Marido da Akie Tatsuo Hatamoto (26)
NDoes he even know we're up to our necks in debt over here?!
Ele sabe que estamos afogados em dívidas?
We have 24 hours until the ship arrives in Tokyo.
Temos 24 horas até o navio chegar em Tóquio.
We simply have to do something before then...
É só uma questão de fazermos alguma coisa até lá...
It's me, Takeshi.
Sou eu, Takeshi.
Enter.
Entre.
Sorry to disturb you.
Desculpe incomodar.
That was an exceptional speech you gave at the wedding.
O seu discurso no casamento foi comovente.
Just what I would expect of the man whom Natsue chose.
Como esperado do homem que a Natsue escolheu.
Thank you...
Obrigado.
Scratching your cheeks when you're embarrassed...
Isso de coçar as bochechas quando fica encabulado...
You're just like him.
Você é igual a ele.
Just like your father, Zaiki Isao!
Ao seu pai, Isao Zaiki!
Falsify your family registry all you want, you still cannot fool me!
Pode falsificar seu registro familiar o quanto quiser, não me engana!
I've known all this time that you joined the company
Sei da sua identidade desde que você entrou na empresa
and got close to Natsue just to avenge your father!
e se aproximou da Natsue só para vingar seu pai!
What is it you're after?
O que você quer?
Money?
Dinheiro?
Or my life, perhaps?
Ou minha vida, talvez?
What's the matter? Why won't you speak?!
O que foi? O gato comeu a sua língua?
Answer me!
Me responda!
These are the main members of the Hatamoto family.
Esses são os principais membros da família Hatamoto.
So all of these people went to your wedding?
Então todos eles foram no seu casamento?
Yes! All nine of them,
Sim, os nove.
Say, Takeshi-san is rather late...
Ei, como o Takeshi está demorando...
Yes. He still hasn't come back from Grandfather's room...
É. Ele ainda não voltou do quarto do vô...
I wonder what happened.
O que será que houve?
Maybe they're discussing some under-the-table business!
Talvez eles estejam fechando acordos velados!
Akie!
Akie, minha irmã!
You're late.
Que demora.
Sorry.
Desculpa.
Dad not here yet?
O pai ainda não chegou?
Hatamoto family butler Suzuki Kenji (64)
Mordomo dos Hatamoto Kenji Suzuki (64)
No, though I am certain he will be here shortly.
Não, mas tenho certeza de que logo ele chega.
You're late, Ichiro-san!
Que demora, Ichiro!
Did you make sure to wash your hands?!
Lavou bem as mãos?
Yes...
Sim...
Say! Do you have a boyfriend, Ran-san?
Ei! Você tem namorado, Ran?
Of course not, she's still a kid...
Claro que não, ela ainda é uma criança...
How rude!
Que falta de educação!
I'll have you know there is someone I like!
Eu estou a fim de uma pessoa!
Right, Conan-kun?
Não é, Conan?
Yeah...
Sim.
Well, he's really smart, good at soccer, dependable, and cool!
Bem, ele é muito inteligente, joga bola bem, é confiável e bacana!
What are you acting so embarrassed about?
Por que está ficando envergonhado?
And he's an even better detective than my dad!
E ele é um detetive melhor do que o meu pai!
You mean your father's a--
Está dizendo que seu pai é...
Oh? I didn't tell you?
Ah, eu não contei?
My dad's a detective!
Meu pai é detetive!
Is something the matter?
Algum problema?
Keep it a secret from my grandfather! He hates detectives!
Não fale pro meu avô. Ele odeia detetives!
He says that people who pry into others' affairs are despicable!
Ele diz que quem se mete na vida alheia é desprezível!
He's right, at least in old man Kogoro's case.
Ele tem razão, pelo menos no caso do velho Kogoro.
Sir? Your seat is ready, sir...
Senhor, seu assento está pronto...
A flower?
Uma flor?
Takeshi-san! You're really late!
Takeshi, mas que demora!
Sorry, I was thinking about some things in my room.
Desculpe, estava no meu quarto pensando na vida.
Are you alright? You look pale.
Você está bem? Está pálido.
Oh? What happened to your flower?
Ah, o que houve com sua flor?
That's strange. Where could I have lost it?
Que estranho. Onde será que perdi?
Sorry to disturb you, sir.
Desculpe incomodar, senhor.
Everyone is waiting for you--
Estão todos esperando por...
Whose voice was that?!
De quem foi essa voz?
The butler's!
Do mordomo!
It came from Dad's room!
Veio do quarto do pai!
What happened, Suzuki-san?!
O que houve, Suzuki?
It's too late. He's dead.
Tarde demais. Ele está morto.
No!
Não!
Grandfather!
Vô!
Stop!
Pare!
Everyone stay out!
Ninguém entre!
Nobody's to enter this room until I say it's okay!
Ninguém pode entrar até eu autorizar!
It would seem that 40 or 50 minutes have passed since Gozo's death.
Parece que se passaram 40 ou 50 minutos da morte do Gozo.
You were the one who found him, Suzuki-san?
Você que o achou, Suzuki?
Yes.
Sim.
Where were you 40 to 50 minutes ago, around 8:00 PM?
Onde você estava há cerca de 40 e 50 minutos, às 20h?
I was getting things ready for dinner at 8:00,
Eu estava fazendo os preparativos para o jantar às 20h,
so I was in the dining room the entire time.
estava na sala de jantar o tempo todo.
I did see Suzuki-san working in a hurry around the tables!
Sim, eu vi o Suzuki mexendo sem parar nas mesas!
The door to this room was locked when you found the body, correct?
A porta deste quarto estava trancada
Yes.
Sim.
What ways are there to lock the door?
Como é possível trancar a porta?
It can be locked from the inside,
Ela pode ser trancada por dentro, mas por fora, é preciso ter a chave.
And this window doesn't open, so it's impossible to sneak into the room.
E a janela não se abre, então não tem como se esgueirar.
In other words, this room was impregnable!
Ou seja, era impossível entrar no quarto!
Impregnable?!
Impossível de entrar?
You're saying that my grandfather committed suicide?!
Está dizendo que o meu avô cometeu suicídio?
But it's strange.
Mas é estranho.
If it was a suicide, then there's something important missing here.
Se foi suicídio, tem algo muito importante faltando aqui.
The weapon.
A arma.
He died of blood loss after being stabbed in the abdomen.
Ele morreu por perda de sangue de uma facada no abdômen.
But the knife used to do it is nowhere to be found.
Mas a faca não está em lugar nenhum.
Are you sure it wasn't a dagger made of ice or anything?
Não foi uma adaga de gelo ou algo assim?
Mystery novels are full of things that melt away and stuff.
Em livros de mistério sempre tem coisas que derretem e tal.
Would someone seriously commit suicide with something like that?
Alguém cometeria suicídio com uma arma dessas?
I bet this is more of his harassment.
Aposto que é mais uma forma de assédio dele.
He wanted to torment us by making every Hatamoto here seem suspect!
Ele queria nos atormentar,
He hated everyone in the family, after all.
Afinal, ele odiava todos da família.
Everyone except Natsue-san, that is.
Todos menos a Natsue, é claro.
Akie!
Akie!
I wouldn't put it past the old man...
Olha, o velho seria capaz de uma coisa dessas...
Then it's decided! It was a suicide!
Então é isso, foi suicídio!
This was a murder.
Foi um assassinato.
What?!
O quê?!
And an extremely simple one, at that.
E um bem simples.
You, again?!
Você de novo?
Here, take a close look at the doorframe!
Dê uma olhada no batente da porta!
See the blood?
Está vendo o sangue?
If the door was closed when he committed suicide,
Se a porta estava fechada quando ele cometeu suicídio,
none of his blood could have landed there.
o sangue não teria parado ali.
So it's more natural to think that he was stabbed while the door was open.
Então é mais natural pensar
That's it! Somebody stabbed Gozo the instant he left the room!
É isso! Alguém apunhalou o Gozo assim que ele saiu do quarto!
Then who locked the door?
Então quem trancou o quarto?
No clue...
Pois é, quem terá sido...?
Hey, you sure you're a detective?
Ei, você é mesmo um detetive?
That's it! It was Mr. Gozo himself who locked the door!
É isso! Foi o próprio Gozo que trancou a porta!
Someone stabbed him outside the room and then kept coming for him,
Alguém o apunhalou fora do quarto e continuou atacando,
so he locked himself inside to escape his attacker!
então ele se trancou para fugir do criminoso!
But then he ran out of strength and died!
Mas ele ficou sem forças e morreu!
I see. That would make the most sense.
Entendi, isso faria sentido.
You're such a great detective!
Você é um grande detetive!
Wait a minute! That means everyone had an opportunity to kill him!
Espere um pouco!
The murder took place at approximately 8:00.
O assassinato se deu por volta das 20h.
Ran, Conan, Natsue-san, and I were at our table since 7:30,
Ran, Conan, Natsue e eu ficamos na mesa desde as 19h30,
The same can be said for Suzuki-san, who was near our table at the time.
O mesmo vale pro Suzuki, que estava perto da mesa no horário.
In other words, since the killer wasn't in the dining room at the time...
Ou seja, como o assassino não estava na sala de jantar na hora...
...it was one of you seven!
...foi um de vocês sete!
Suzuki-san.
Suzuki.
When you entered the room, did you notice anything out of the ordinary?
Você reparou algo fora do comum ao entrar no quarto?
No, nothing in particular...
Não, nada em particular...
Oh, now that you mention it, I found this flower in front of the door...
Ah, pensando bem, esta flor estava na frente da porta...
Flower?
Flor?
That's the flower I put on Takeshi-san's jacket!
É a flor que eu pus no paletó do Takeshi!
Come to think of it, you were really late coming to the dining room.
Pensando bem, você demorou bastante para vir à sala de jantar.
No, I was just thinking about things in my room...
Não, eu estava pensando na vida no meu quarto...
Don't try to deny it, Takeshi-san.
Não tente negar, Takeshi.
I happened to hear you and Father shouting in his room!
Eu ouvi você e o pai gritando no quarto dele!
I thought I was going to faint
Eu achei que ia desmaiar...
when I heard that you're actually the son of Zaiki Isao!
quando soube que você é, na verdade, filho de Isao Zaiki!
Who's Zaiki Isao?
Quem é Isao Zaiki?
He committed suicide when Gozo took over his company 10 years ago.
Ele cometeu suicídio
One year later, his wife died of an illness,
Um ano mais tarde, a esposa dele morreu de uma doença,
and their only son was apparently placed in an institution.
e seu único filho foi colocado num orfanato.
To think that that was Takeshi-kun!
Quem diria que era o Takeshi!
Is it true, Takeshi-san?!
É verdade, Takeshi?
Takeshi-san!
Takeshi!
Yeah. I'm Zaiki Takeshi, son of Zaiki Isao!
É. Sou Takeshi Zaiki, filho de Isao Zaiki!
But I...!
Mas eu...
...Got close to Natsue-san so you could avenge your father?
Se aproximou da Natsue para poder vingar o seu pai?
You decided to become a member of the Hatamoto family
Decidiu fazer parte da família Hatamoto
and wait for the chance to kill Gozo.
e ter uma chance de matar o Gozo.
And then tonight, you did just that!
E, hoje, a oportunidade surgiu!
No! I didn't kill him!
Não, eu não o matei!
Natsue! Wait!
Natsue, espere!
I had you pegged as a pretty staunch fellow,
Eu sempre te achei um cara íntegro,
but it looks like I was wrong.
mas parece que me equivoquei.
Joji-san!
Joji!
You gotta be an idiot to drop your flower at the crime scene!
Tem que ser muito burro pra derrubar sua flor na cena do crime!
I didn't, I lost my flower somewhere!
Eu não derrubei! Quando vi, estava sem a flor!
There are wiped blood stains on the outside carpet...
Há manchas de sangue apagadas no carpete de fora...
Say, was that flower really here on the floor?
Ei, a flor estava mesmo aqui no chão?
Yes, that's right, little boy.
Estava sim, garotinho.
What's this?
O que é isso?
A bread crumb!
Migalha de pão!
A bread crumb lying in a pool of blood?
Migalha de pão no meio de uma poça de sangue?
What's it mean?!
O que isso significa?
Say, Mr. Butler.
Ei, tio mordomo.
Was there bread during the wedding banquet this afternoon?
Teve pão no banquete de almoço do casamento?
But of course--it was an extravagant French meal.
Mas é claro. Foi uma refeição de alta culinária francesa.
Joji-sama made it all himself. He runs his own French restaurant.
O próprio Joji que preparou. Ele tem um restaurante francês.
Did everyone eat it?
Todos comeram?
Yes. Everyone but Gozo-sama.
Sim. Todos menos o Sr. Gozo.
He loathed Western-style food.
Ele abominava a culinária ocidental.
He said that just looking at bread would make him nauseous.
Dizia que passava mal só de olhar pra pão.
If Joji-san's a chef, he has kitchen knives of his own, right?
Já que o Joji é um chef, ele tem facas de cozinha, correto?
Naturally. Chefs like him always own their own set.
Mas é claro. Chefs como ele sempre têm as melhores facas.
Come now, children shouldn't pry into other people's business.
Ei, crianças não devem se meter na vida alheia.
Get in there!
Entra!
Cool off in this storeroom for a while.
Sossega um pouco na despensa.
Open up! Please!
Abram, por favor! Não fui eu!
Don't be stupid, you murderer!
Não diga besteira, seu assassino!
We're giving you to the police the minute we arrive in Tokyo tomorrow!
Vamos entregá-lo pra polícia assim que chegarmos em Tóquio amanhã!
Better get ready!
É melhor se preparar!
His motive and all the evidence is more than enough, right, Detective?
O motivo e todas as provas são
He had more than enough motive.
Motivo ele tinha de sobra.
And if his fingerprints are found on the murder weapon, it's in the bag.
E as digitais dele estavam na arma do crime, na sacola.
Here you are.
Aqui está.
Thank you!
Obrigada!
Here you go, little boy.
Aqui está, garotinho.
You sure are lucky, Mariko.
Como você tem sorte, Mariko.
Now that Takeshi-san has killed the old man,
Agora que o Takeshi matou o velho,
he'll never make that stupid announcement about his inheritance!
ele não vai fazer o anúncio idiota sobre a herança!
That's true.
Verdade.
Now the Hatamoto Group will belong to you,
Agora, o Grupo Hatamoto vai ser seu,
And you can draw as much as you want,
E você pode desenhar à vontade
now that your grandfather's dead, Ichiro-san!
agora que o seu vô morreu, Ichiro!
And eventually, you too will become the Hatamoto Group's--
E, algum dia, você também será o herdeiro do...
I don't really want that...
Não quero isso.
Hey, you ain't thinkin' of monopolizing the guy's inheritance, are ya?
Ei, não diga que você está pensando
Don't worry! All you grandchildren will get--
Não se preocupe! Todos os netos vão receber...
Could you not talk about money on the night of our father's death?
Poderia não falar de dinheiro na noite da morte do nosso pai?
Who're you to talk? You left the family to go be a chef!
Olha só quem fala! Abandonou a família para virar chef.
I know that Father flat out refused you
Sei que o pai disse "não" na sua cara
You wanted his money too! So be grateful!
Você também queria o dinheiro dele, então seja honesto!
Um...
Bem...
I'm extremely sorry to say this,
Eu sinto muito dizer isso,
but your father wrote up a will
mas seu pai escreveu um testamento
just in case something was to happen to him...
para caso algo acontecesse com ele...
What?!
O quê?!
I believe it will be read at the main office in the next few days.
A leitura será feita no escritório central em alguns dias.
Does that mean--?
Isso quer dizer que...
All of his fortune goes to--
Toda a fortuna dele vai para...
Natsue?!
a Natsue?!
Yes.
Sim.
And leadership of the Hatamoto Group is to be given to the man
E a liderança do Grupo Hatamoto será dada
that Natsue-san chose.
ao homem que a Natsue escolher.
This can't be!
Não pode ser!
What? Then what the hell did I marry Akie for?!
O quê? Então por que eu me casei com a Akie?
Don't tell me you only married me to get my dad's money!
Não diga que só se casou comigo
That's right! Why else would I live with a tight-fisted bitch like you?!
Isso mesmo! Senão nunca me casaria com uma carrancuda feito você!
Who're you to talk?! You're just a worthless musician!
Olha só quem fala! Você não passa de um músico falido!
Go and get a real job!
Arranja um emprego de verdade!
Natsue-san?
Natsue?
What are you doing out here?
O que você está fazendo aqui?
Nothing, just thinking.
Nada, só pensando.
About Takeshi-san?
Sobre o Takeshi?
I trusted him...
Eu confiei nele...
But he only married me so he could kill my grandfather!
Mas ele só se casou comigo para matar o meu avô!
I'll never trust anyone again!
Nunca mais vou confiar nas pessoas!
I trust him.
Eu confio nele.
My gut feeling tells me that he's not a bad person.
Algo me diz que ele não é má pessoa.
He's the one you chose, after all.
Afinal, ele foi o homem que você escolheu.
He couldn't possibly be a bad person!
Não tem como ele ser uma má pessoa!
Ran-san...
Ran...
Hey, what are you--
Ei, o que você...
Hey, did you hear anything strange just now?
Ei, ouviram um barulho estranho?
Did you hear anything, Natsue-san?
Ouviu alguma coisa, Natsue?
No...
Não...
No, I did hear something!
Não, eu ouvi alguma coisa!
The sound of something falling into the water
O som de algo caindo na água
and then a weird thud from the deck below!
e um baque estranho do deck abaixo!
Conan-kun!
Conan!
Wait, Conan-kun! What's going on?!
Espere, Conan! O que foi?
What's gotten into you two--?
O que deu em vocês dois?
The cause of death was most likely brain damage
A causa da morte mais provável é dano cerebral causado por um golpe na cabeça.
Judging from the wound,
A julgar pela ferida,
the murder weapon was a steel pipe or something similar.
a arma do crime foi um cano de aço ou algo parecido.
Who would do something this terrible?!
Quem faria uma coisa dessas?
Don't tell me Takeshi's struck again!
Não diga que é obra do Takeshi de novo!
Impossible. He was locked in.
Não tem como, ele está trancado.
Hey! Conan!
Ei, Conan!
The door's unlocked!
A porta está aberta!
Out of the way!
Saia da frente!
He's gone!
Sumiu!
He wasn't in the storeroom?!
Ele não estava da despensa?
We most certainly locked him inside, but he's nowhere to be found.
Com toda certeza a gente o trancou, mas ele não está em lugar algum.
So Takeshi was the one who killed Father and Tatsuo-san!
Então foi o Takeshi que matou o pai e o Tatsuo!
The thud that Conan heard
O baque que o Conan ouviu
was probably the sound of the killer hitting Tatsuo-san.
devia ser o assassino acertando o Tatsuo.
The splash he heard
O som de água
was either the sound of the murder weapon being thrown overboard, or...
ou foi o som da arma do crime sendo jogada ou...
...the sound of the killer jumping into the water
...o som do assassino pulando na água
after running out of places to hide!
por não ter para onde correr!
Takeshi-san...
Takeshi...
At any rate, there's still a high possibility
Enfim, ainda é bastante provável
that there's a killer aboard this ship.
que haja um assassino a bordo deste navio.
Let's all withdraw to the dining room for now.
Vamos todos para a sala de jantar por ora.
Are you saying he could be trying to kill me?!
Está dizendo que ele pode estar tentando me matar?
Have you forgotten?!
Você já se esqueceu?
His motive for murder was to exact revenge on Hatamoto Gozo,
Ele matou para se vingar do Gozo Hatamoto,
who drove his father to suicide 10 years ago!
que levou o pai ao suicídio há dez anos!
But for all we know...
Mas, até onde sabemos...
...he could be trying to kill everyone in the Hatamoto family!
...ele pode estar tentando matar todos da família Hatamoto!
I know that you have another man!
Sei que você tem outro homem!
You're the one who wants the inheritance the most!
Você é quem mais quer a herança!
Even Ichiro was mad at him
Até o Ichiro estava irritado com ele
for tearing up his prize-winning drawing!
por rasgar o desenho premiado!
Ichiro!
Ichiro!
My leg!
Minha perna!
This is my knife...
Esta é a minha faca...
All of these mysteries are connected by one thread!
Todos os mistérios estão ligados por um fio!
On the next Conan--
No próximo episódio de Conan...
Next Conan's Hint:
Dica do próximo Conan:
Sketch book.
Caderno de desenho.
Next episode is interesting right from the start.
O próximo é divertido desde a abertura.
So exciting!
Não vejo a hora!